{
    "id": "b5985aa059da443893b893acbc4c1ac5",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This country is backward ………………….. many areas.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7228e1aae5894f2ab2e71ac18670f39b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think that we can count ....................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d3e41e3a3d647cb9eeada9a15dc02e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t believe ………………….. ghosts. Do you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd67ba8e05a34df98c9611ec70962471"
        },
        {
            "question": "Beware ..................... . dogs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7bd28780fc7a49e797996efe95fb1eaf"
        },
        {
            "question": "During his regime, the king brought …………………. many radical reforms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "about",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "123ea5df263e4da587aa1828bd1139a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are anxious ..................... . an end to this misunderstanding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ffc98d542ded4e16931fe402796bd56b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is quite good ..................... .. remembering dates.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45c3302777114c29a6528a4410f657c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was green .................. envy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3b9a5287f89540eeb63b2403dddd4148"
        },
        {
            "question": "My hands were blue .....................… cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8997d0352fb748c184392e660ffd1e8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We congratulated him ...................... his success.",
            "description": "On and for are both possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e5b594500eef4d3387626db663e7d07e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly he complained ………………….. chest pain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8522b4eb382243e4961767ce5ebab8ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "Contrary .....................… our expectations the central bank increased interest rates.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0220b9feed3a4bffb360323d1a8f810f"
        }
    ]
}